Generated by ai-sub version: 0.0.1
Config: (
"rpm": 5,
"tpm": 250000,
"model": "gemini-2.5-flash",
"thinking_budget": 24576,
"max_subtitle_chars": 60,
"num_processing_threads": 4,
"num_upload_threads": 4,
"split_seconds": 180
)
Prompt Template: You are an expert subtitling and transcription AI. Your primary task is to generate precise, contextually rich English and Japanese subtitles for the provided video content.
**Key Principles & Requirements:**
1.  **TIMING ACCURACY (ABSOLUTE HIGHEST PRIORITY):**
*   **Ensure the `start` and `end` timestamps for each subtitle entry is meticulously accurate.** They must align perfectly with the *actual beginning and end of the spoken words* for that specific segment.
*   Timestamps must always be in `mm:ss` (minutes:seconds).
2.  **CRITICAL: Holistic Translation, Contextual Understanding & Comprehensive Analysis:**
*   **You ABSOLUTELY MUST watch the entire video thoroughly** to understand the visual context, speaker actions, and overall narrative.
*   **When a single logical sentence or phrase is split across multiple subtitle entries (e.g., due to timing or character limits), you MUST mentally combine these parts to understand the full, complete meaning before translating.**
*   **NEVER translate individual subtitle entries in isolation if they are part of a larger, continuous thought or sentence.** The translation for each entry must be a coherent and accurate part of the complete, overarching sentence.
*   Analyze *all* spoken dialogue in the video to produce highly accurate and complete transcriptions.
*   For songs or singing sections, prioritize on-screen lyrics in the video for subtitles over transcribing the singing.
*   If the audio is noisy or unclear, leverage *all* contextual cues (visuals from the video, surrounding dialogue) to infer and generate the most probable dialogue.
*   Utilize the comprehensive understanding gained from *watching the entire video* to enhance the accuracy of transcriptions, translations, and overall subtitle quality. This includes understanding nuances, resolving ambiguities, and ensuring the subtitle content aligns perfectly with what is happening visually.
*   **Example:**
*   Original Japanese: "なんでも打ち明けられるママにも" (Subtitle 1) + "言えないことも全部" (Subtitle 2)
*   Incorrect Translation (isolated): "You're like a mom I can confide anything in." + "Even things I can't say to anyone else."
*   Correct Translation (holistic): "I can confide everything," (Subtitle 1) + "everything I can't even tell my mum." (Subtitle 2)
3.  **Dual Language Provision & Translation Quality:**
*   Provide both English and Japanese subtitles for *all* spoken dialogue.
*   If the original dialogue is in English, transcribe it and provide an accurate, natural-sounding Japanese translation.
*   If the original dialogue is in Japanese, transcribe it and provide an accurate, natural-sounding English translation.
*   Ensure translations are culturally appropriate and maintain the original meaning, tone, and intent, taking into account the full context of the video and any split sentences.
4.  **Readability & Formatting:**
* Long sentences MUST be split into multiple, shorter subtitle entries, each with its own start and end time, for better readability on screen. Each subtitle entry (english and japanese) MUST be a maximum of (max_subtitle_chars) characters. Do not use newline characters within a single subtitle entry.
** Output Format **
* Your entire response must be a single JSON object.
* Timestamps must always be in `mm:ss` (minutes:seconds).
** Example Output **
```json
((
"subtitles": [
"start": "00:00",
"end": "00:04",
"english": "Hello everyone, and welcome to our presentation.",
"japanese": "皆様、プレゼンテーションへようこそ。"
)),
((
"start": "00:05",
"end": "00:06",
"english": "Today, we'll be discussing the future of AI",
"japanese": "本日は、AIの未来について"
)),
((
"start": "00:06",
"end": "00:08",
"english": "and its impact on various industries worldwide.",
"japanese": "その影響について議論します。"
)),
((
"start": "00:09",
"end": "00:11",
"english": "It's a very important topic for all of us.",
"japanese": "これは私たち全員にとって非常に重要なテーマです。"
)),
((
"start": "00:11",
"end": "00:14",
"english": "We sincerely appreciate your attendance today.",
"japanese": "本日はご出席いただき誠にありがとうございます。"
))
]
```
偶然が いくつも
Many coincidences
かさなりあって
overlapping
あなたと 出会って
Meeting you
恋に 落ちた
I fell in love
聞こえそうな 鼓動が
My heartbeat, which seems to be heard,
恥ずかしいよ
is embarrassing.
どうして 私らしくは
Why am I
ないよ
not acting like myself?
今日が 終わっても
Even if today ends
明日が 過ぎても
Even if tomorrow passes
いつも そばにいて
Always be by my side
ずっと 素直に変わらぬ
Two people who will always be
二人
honest and unchanged
信じたい
I want to believe
あなたと会った あの日から
From the day I met you
どんなときにも
No matter when,
すべてを 感じられる
I feel like I can
気がする
feel everything.
ただあなたが
Just by you
いるだけで
being here
そばにいるだけで
Just by being by my side
Forever You're My Only Feeling Heart
夕暮れが 夜風を
The twilight cools
ひやしていくよ
down the night breeze.
あなたと いるから
Because I'm with you,
寒くないよ
I'm not cold.
街の色が きれいに
The city lights start
ともりだして
to beautifully glow.
私も 変わり始めてる
I'm also starting
よ
to change.
雲が 晴れてても
Even if the clouds clear
この上に映る 星は少な
The stars reflecting above
くて
are few.
いつか一緒に満天の空
Someday I want to look up
見上げたい
at the starry sky with you.
奇跡が起こるような
Like a miracle is
そんな
happening.
星空の下で
Under the starry sky,
あなたと
with you,
同じ未来を歩いて
walking towards the same future.
二人が信じ合うことが
When two people trust each other,
愛し合うことね
that is loving each other.
Forever You're My Only Feeling Heart
You're My Only Feeling Heart
Feeling Heart